该起床了
It's time.
小乖乖
Hey there...
你起来干嘛？
Hey. What are you doing up?
是爸爸吗？
Is that Daddy?
嗨，女牛仔
Hey there, cowgirl.
她今天很调皮
She's a little feisty today.
小宝宝应该多睡觉
Babies should be sleeping.
我肚子太饿了
"I'm too hungry for my own good." Yes.
我要去准备了
I gotta get ready.
今天可不能丢东忘西
Wrong day to be forgetting stuff.
大家都说你很幸运，别搞砸
You know how lucky you are. Don't screw this up.
好啦
All right! Jesus.
她睡了吗？
She go back to sleep?
睡了，她吃撑了
Yes. Ate like a pig.
我知道我很幸运
I know I'm lucky.
今天通过考验，前途就无量
I ace this job, the department's wide open.
搞不好哪天能当分局长
Get my own division someday.
他们都住豪宅
You should see their houses.
哈罗
Hello?
对
Well, yes.
放心，我会的
Don't worry, I will.
对，他在
He's right here. It's Alonzo.
霍特？ 是，长官
-Hello. -Hoyt? -Yes, sir.
你要去局里报到吗？
Going to roll call?
我正要出门
I'm leaving now.
霍特 是，长官
-Hoyt? -Yes, sir?
巡警才去报到，我们不必去
Fairies go to roll call. We don't.
那很好
Good to know.
十点钟到七街口咖啡店碰面
There's a coffee shop on 7th. Be there at 10.
穿便衣、跑鞋
Be in comfortable shoes.
多带一把枪，你有吗？
Got a backup gun?
没有，我只有贝瑞塔警枪
Only the standard issue Beretta.
连手铐一起带着
Bring it. Cuffs too.
也许进办公室，但先去抓毒犯 这是顶尖的缉毒小组
Maybe we'll do some business. We're aggressive.
所以我才自愿加入
I know. That's why I signed up.
我只想谢谢你…
I want to thank you for this--
怎么了？
What's wrong?
这好像第一天参加足球集训
Feels like football tryouts.
真希望今天就知道有没有通过
I wish it was tomorrow so I'd know if I made the squad.
今天是好日子
Listen, it's not tomorrow, it's today.
你一定会通过考验
I know it's gonna work out.
真的吗？
You do?
早安，长官
Good morning, sir.
不，谢了
No, thank you, ma'am.
办正事前先吃早饭，我请客
Get some chow in you. My dollar.
谢谢你，我吃过了
Thank you, sir, but I ate.
好吧，随你便
Fine. Don't.
这儿挺好的
It's nice here.
我想好好看报
May I read?
对不起，长官
I'm sorry, sir. I--
谢谢
Thank you.
我点东西吃好了
I'll get something to eat.
不行，你错过机会了
Hell, no you won't. You fucked up.
我想看报纸，请你闭嘴
I'm trying to read. Please shut up.
不必坐在像烤箱的警车真好
I'll like not being in a hot black and white all summer.
跟我说一个故事
Tell me a story, Hoyt.
我的故事？
Like my story?
不是，是说一个故事
Not your story, a story.
你不肯乖乖闭嘴让我看报
Since you can't shut up so I can read,
就说故事给我听
tell me a story.
我不会说故事
I don't know any.
你不会说故事？
You don't?
不会 好吧，那我说给你听
-No. -I'll tell you one.
这是份报纸
This is a newspaper, right?
九成都是废话，但很有娱乐性
It's 90 percent bullshit. But it's entertaining. So I read it.
我看报就是要娱乐一下
It entertains me.
你一直烦我，那就换你娱乐我
You won't let me read it, so you entertain me.
说故事给我听，快点
Tell me a story now. Go.
有一次我拦下酒醉驾驶 酒醉驾驶吗？
-There was a DUI stop. -A DUI stop?
我最好赶快掏出枪来
Let me load up!
醉汉好危险哦
-A DUI? Oh, shit! -Well, I--
很精采，我们在巡逻
Listen, we were on midwatch--
你们？
We who?
我和黛比 黛比是谁？
-Oh, me and Debbie. -Who's Debbie?
黛比麦斯薇，我的训练官
Debbie Maxwell, my training officer.
女训练官？
A female training officer?
是的
Yes, sir.
好极了，太好了
Okay. All right.
她是黑人或白人？
Was she black, white?
白人
She was white.
她有没有搞头？
Lick-her license?
什么？
A what?
她是不是女同性恋？
A lick-her license. Was she a dyke, a lesbian?
她行不行？
Is she any good?
她挺厉害的
She's pretty good.
黛比很棒，进行巡逻，说吧
-Okay, Debbie, midwatch. Go. -Right.
那晚很平静
-It was a quiet night-- -Boom!
你要随时接受震撼教育
-What the fuck? -You never know, that's the point. Go.
我们正在巡逻，我开车
It was quiet and we're rolling...
一辆本田房车从巷子冲出来
...I'm driving. This Acura, just a beautiful car...
超速冲越了中隔线
...comes out a side street, all over the median.
于是我亮警灯、鸣警笛
I hit the wailer.
他继续开了十个街口才停车
He drives for 10 blocks before he pulls over.
我测量了酒精浓度就逮捕他
Plates run clean, so I test and arrest.
我把他押上警车，黛比去搜车
I'm belting in our unit, and she's tossing his car.
找到一把手枪和两把散弹枪 装了子弹上了膛
She shows me a .38 and two loaded shotguns.
真的还假的？ 我不盖你
-No shit? -No shit! So...
她呼叫总部，我继续搜索
...she calls and I'm searching.
结果找到五百公克的安非他命
I find 500 grams of meth.
这砘锸潜Ｊ统鲇的烟毒犯
Turns out he's on bail for distribution...
他正要去把他的前合伙人干掉
...on his way to smoke his ex-partner before trial.
我们阻止一起谋杀案
Prevented a murder.
你逮到他，真了不起
You got him. It's amazing.
是真的
It is. That you're out there...
你跟霹雳娇娃一起巡逻一年
...with a fine bitch for a year and the best story you can tell me...
最得意的故事竟然是拦下醉汉
...is a drunk stop.
我不相信你
But I don't believe you.
你一定有跟她上床
You tapped that ass, didn't you?
老实说，你一定搞过她
Tell the truth. You know you tapped that ass.
你们在后座就做了起来
In the back, bam! Code X.
我有老婆
I got a wife.
你也有老二
You got a dick.
不是吗？
You do have one, don't you?
是的
Yes.
你的老二在裤档，左右有口袋
Your dick lines up straight. Right and left of it are pockets.
口袋里有钱，把钱掏出来 你买单
In those pockets are money. Look in either one. Pay the bill.
帮我把传单拿走
Grab that menu off that window for me.
上车，车门没锁
Get in, it's unlocked.
丢进置物柜
Throw that in the glove box.
这辆车不是警方用车
This is not from the motor pool.
不是，不过很拉风，对吧？
No. Sexy, though, huh?
办公室在分局吗？
Where's the office, at division?
这就是办公室
You're in the office.
起来了
Going up.
今天是训练日，霍特警官
Today is a training day.
我要带你到街头办案
Give you a taste of the business.
我有38起案子等着开庭
I got 38 cases pending trial...
有63起正在办
...63 active investigations,
有250起破不了案
250 I can't clear.
我有五个手下，性格南辕北辙
I supervise five officers. Five personalities.
你表现得好就是第六个
Five sets of problems. You could be six.
但我不会特别照顾你
I ain't holding no hands.
你只有今天能证明你的能耐
You got today to show me what you're made of.
不想缉毒就滚下车
You don't like Narcotics, get the fuck out of my car...
就回办公室处理文件
...get a job
追讨厂商支票，你懂吗？
chasing bad checks. You hear me?
我懂 很好
-I hear you. -Okay.
你为什么想参加缉毒组？
Why do you want to be a narc?
我想铲除毒枭，为社会服务
To serve my community by ridding it of dangerous drugs.
你真正的理由是什么？
Right, but why a narc?
我想升警探
I want to make detective.
这就对了，跟着我就没问题
Stick with me, you can do it.
忘了警校学的那一套
Unlearn that academy shit.
乖乖守规矩在街头肯定送命
Don't bring that here. It'll get you killed.
你要我做什么我都做
I'll do anything you want me to do.
好兄弟
My nigger.
先把车窗摇下来
Roll your window down. Start there.
熟悉街头的声音、味道和感觉
-Got to hear it, smell it, taste it. -Right.
你会说西班牙话吗？
How's your Espao.
一定要学，学了能保命
Learn that shit. That will get you killed.
那些流氓会在背后暗算你
They plot all kinds of shit behind your back.
你打算教我抓了嫌犯…
You gonna teach me that old-school Rodney King shit?
就狠狠打一顿那一套吗？
We don't roll like that no more.
那一套不管用了
Now we use this.
一定要动脑筋，他们太强悍了
These niggers are too strong.
你认为我疯了，是吗？
Think I'm crazy?
我根本搞不清状况
I don't know what to think.
是吗？ 是
-Yeah? -Yeah.
很好
Good.
那就好
你结婚多久？
Been married long?
一年了
-About a year. -Yeah?
有小孩吗？
You got a kid?
小女儿，九个月大
A girl, 9 months.
我有四个
I got four.
都是儿子
Boys.
想生儿子就让我帮你老婆
You need a son, I'll hook your lady up.
保证生儿子
Can't miss.
请不要谈我家人
Can we not talk about my family, all right?
我尊重你
I respect that.
我也结婚了，也有美娇娘
I'm married, I got my queen too.
新婚夫妻总是如胶如漆 你们做爱一定面对面
I remember having a young bride. You probably fuck her face-to-face, don't you?
别提起我老婆
Let's not talk about her.
这就是重点，你很爱你的家人
That's my point. You're so in love, it's coming right out.
办案时你有顾虑就回不了家
The day you bring that here is the day...
你要隐藏这份感情
...you don't make it back. Hide it deep inside of you.
否则这些人渣就会用来威胁你
The maggots out here will find it use it against you and chew you up.
别戴婚戒来办案
Never wear the ring to work.
我是说真的 好啦，谢了
-I'm serious about that. -Thanks.
为何停在这里？
What's here?
毒品交易
Transactions.
你看到那个帮派小混混吗？
You see that guy
他假装没在卖大麻
trying to act like he's not slanging dope?
对
Yeah.
他是我的手下
That's my boy.
他是我的手下，他叫奈托
That's my boy, Neto.
他才十七岁就是狠角色
Only 17, but he can kill.
他替我工作
Works for me.
他是线人吗？
He's an informer?
我到处都有眼线
Teammate. I got eyes everywhere.
我让他卖大麻，赚点钱养家
He gets to make some cash. Lets me know when big things happen.
有大买卖时他就告诉我
Big transactions.
你相信他？ 当然了
-You trust him? -Damn right I do.
我帮他老妈留在美国 来了，来了，仔细看了
Sprung his mom from INS detention. Here we go. Watch this.
很好
That's right.
来吧
Come on down.
你看，很精采吧
Come on. Look at it. Sexy, ain't it?
这就对了
That's right.
你看到货脱手了吗？ 看到了
-See the hand-to-hand? -I saw it.
你上次几时逮过嫌犯？
When was your last felony stop?
两礼拜前
Two weeks ago.
你得多练习
You need practice.
他们好像大学生
College kids.
他们要接受震撼教育
They'll get an education today.
先叫他们举手，我在前你在后
I want them grabbing glass. You take the back.
别向总部报告
Stay off of the Rover.
这群臭小子 跑呀，臭小子
-You little fuckers. -Run, baby, run.
警察！手举起来！
Police! Let's see your hands!
举起来 看前面
Put them up! Put them up!
你们两个，手放在挡风玻璃上
Put your hands on the windshield!
用左手把排档换到停车档 这是手排车
-Put your hands on the glass. -Driver, put it in park! -It's a stick shift!
钥匙丢出来，双手放在胸口
Throw the keys out the window!
把手放在胸口
Put your hands on your chest!
交出来吧，小子
All right, fork it over.
少装了，把大麻交出来 快交出来
-What? -You know. The marijuana. Give it to me!
好啦
Give it!
对不起
Okay! Sorry, sir.
闭嘴，地上的烟斗也给我
Shut up! Give me that pipe.
这是我老妈的
My mom gave me that pipe.
管你的，叫她到牢里拿
She can pick it up in jail.
香烟也给我，拿来
Give me the cigarettes too.
给我看好嫌犯
Control your suspect!
小姐，手放在玻璃窗上
Palms on the glass!
你敢乱动，我就赏你一巴掌
Move the hands, I'll slap you!
把脸帖在玻璃上，快点
Face against the glass! Right there!
你们干嘛来这里？ 这是帮派地盘
You know this is a gang neighborhood?
知道这里是帮派地盘吗？
别来这里
-Yeah! -Then don't come down here.
下次再让我逮到
I see you down here again,
我就逼你们走路回家
I'll make you walk home.
那些流氓会轮暴你女友
I'll let the homeboys run a train on her.
你知道吗？
Know what that is?
是，长官，知道了
Yes, sir.
好吧，各位
All right, gentlemen.
谢谢你们的合作
Thanks for your cooperation.
走吧，把枪收起来
Let's go. Safe your iron, son.
可恶
Shit!
好过瘾
I like that shit.
你刚才的表现不错
I like how you move.
你被训练得很好，你瞧瞧
You were trained well. Check that out.
劣等货，夹杂了小颗粒
It's a bad dime. See the hairs, undeveloped seeds.
叶子根本就没长好
You see how immature it is.
墨西哥大麻，这是垃圾 给我看
That's classic Mexican garbage.
好像放太久了，去年的货吧
Let me see. It's old. Probably last year's.
优秀的缉毒干员
To be truly effective...
一定要了解和热爱毒品
...a good narcotics agent must know and love narcotics.
最优秀的缉毒干员
A good narcotics agent should have...
一定要尝尝毒品的味道
...narcotics in his blood.
你要抽吗？
What, you gonna smoke that?
不，你要抽
No, you are.
我才不抽
-Hell if I am! -Yes.
你不抽？ 不抽
-You're not? -No.
你是摩门教徒吗？
Why? You a Mormon?
我会丢掉工作的
I'm not losing my job.
这就是你的工作 我办不到
This is your job.
快抽
-Smoke it. -No.
这不是考试，吸一口
This ain't a test. Take a hit.
我当警察是为了阻止人吸毒
Listen, I became a cop to stop people from using--
这又不是可卡因，吸一口吧
That ain't cocaine. Take a hit.
不要
No, man.
老天爷
Jesus Christ!
你完了
Yeah, right.
我若是毒贩，你这样早就死了
If I was a dealer, you'd be dead!
你会因公殉职，你有毛病吗？
Turn shit down out here, and your wife gets a flag.
我不要你加入我的缉毒小组
You know what? I don't want you in my unit.
滚下车，回去坐办公室吧
Get the fuck out of my car, rookie.
孬种
Poo butt-ass.
拿给我
-What's the holdup? -Move it! Give me that thing.
我要抽，给我吧
I'll smoke it. Give it to me.
你要我抽，我就抽
You want me to, I'll smoke it.
你的初体验
Virgin lungs. Man up now. Man up, nigger. Man up.
用力吸，有种一点
Go ahead. Get it.
你都没吸到，多吸几口
Come on!
给我闭嘴，乖乖地等
Shut the fuck up and just wait!
带点种，快吸呀
-Man the fuck up! Finish that shit! -Geronimo.
好吧，走了
Let's go, nigger. Let's go.
天啊
Oh, shit!
你还好吧？
You okay, kid?
你吸了蛮多的
That's a man size hit you took.
你几时抽过大麻？
When's the last time you smoked weed?
高三那年
The last-- Twelfth grade.
我们…
We were....
抽大麻
-Well, we were.... -Smoking weed.
对
-Yeah. -Yeah.
你没老实跟局里说
Left that out of your service jacket.
你有秘密，大家都有秘密
I know you got secrets. Everybody got secrets.
没想到你爱这玩意
Didn't know you liked it wet, though.
什么玩意？
What's wet?
神仙粉
Butt-naked. Ill.
天使尘
Sherm. Dust.
PCP，苯环利定
PCP. Primos.
俗称P毒品
P-dog.
你抽的就是这玩意
That's what you had.
你尝不出来？
You couldn't taste it?
我没抽过
I never done it.
现在有了，我没有，你有
I haven't, but you have now.
该死
Shit!
今天要验尿，我会被开除的
Shit. I'll get piss-tested, and I'll get fired.
队长一礼拜前已警告我们
The boss has our back. We know before we piss.
可恶
Shit!
Boom!
你为什么要害我？
Why did you do this?
你是大人，没人逼你嗑药
You're an adult. Nobody made you smoke.
这是你自己的决定
You made a decision. Live with it.
我又没拿枪逼你
Not like I put a gun to your head.
真是的
Man....
你最好振作一点
-Oh, man, shit. -Come on, get your shit together now.
这是我线人的家
This is my dog's house.
我让他看看你
We'll see what he thinks of you.
快进来吧
Get your ass in here!
罗杰，怎么样？
Roger, what's up?
最近好吗？握个手吧
-How are they treating you? -All right.
我没吵醒你吧？
I didn't wake you up?
你知道我不睡觉的
I never sleep.
我的新手下杰克
Right. This my new guy, Jake.
进来吧
Come on. Get in here.
我也想喝一杯，你喝什么？
Yeah. Time to get my swerve on here! What you drinking?
最好的酒
The best.
当然了，你一定喝最顶级的
The best, I know. Best for the best.
听说你在赌城惹了事
I heard about Vegas.
有人要追杀你
Got a green light on your ass.
没事了
No problem.
俄国佬要你的命，我会保护你
Russians want you. I got your back.
我知道，谢了
I know that. Thank you.
来
Here.
喝两口吧
Get that medicine up in you.
祝你健康
-Back to the world. -Back to the world.
你干嘛找来一个菜鸟？
Went and got yourself a daisy-fresh rookie.
老天，他嗑过药了
He's high as a motherfucker.
你给他嗑什么药？
What did you give him?
上好的墨西哥大麻
-A little of Mexico's finest. -Yeah.
垃圾
Garbage.
你在哪儿长大？
Where'd you grow up?
北好莱坞
North Hollywood.
你姓什么？
What's your last name?
霍特
Hoyt.
霍特…
Hoyt. Hoyt....
北好莱坞高中美式足球队
Strong safety, North Hollywood High.
没错
Right.
你怎么知道？
How'd you know that?
是呀，你怎么知道？
How did you?
好球员我都记得
-I follow all the good players. -No doubt.
对不起
Excuse me. Shit.
美式足球，是吗？
Strong safety, huh?
干嘛？
It's me. What's up?
我也没辄，你自己看着办
I can't do anything. Clean up your own mess. Don't call me.
我有一个笑话
Hey! Here's a joke, boy.
一个人出门看到门口有只蜗牛
Man walks out of his house, sees this snail lying on his porch.
他把它检起来用力丢到后院
So he picks it up, chucks it into the backyard.
蜗牛撞到一块石头
Snail bounces off a rock, busts its shell up all to shit...
摔破了壳，掉到草地上
...lands in the grass.
蜗牛奄奄一息地躺着
Snail lies there dying.
但是它没死，它开始慢慢爬
But...snail doesn't die. Soon it can crawl again.
有一天
And one day...
它又朝着门口一步一步爬
...snail heads back to the front of the house.
转眼间一年就过去
Finally, after about a year...
它终于又爬到门口
...the little guy crawls back on the porch.
房子的主人要出门上班
Right then the man walks out of his house...
他又看到那只蜗牛
...sees this snail again.
他看了它一眼说
So he looks at it...and he says:
你有毛病呀？
"The fuck's your problem?"
不好笑，真的不好笑
That's not funny.
那你干嘛笑？
What you laughing for then?
我不知道
-I don't know, man. I-- -Hey!
想通这笑话就能搞懂道上规矩
Figure that joke out, you'll figure the streets out.
没什么好想的，这全是废话
Nothing to figure out. It's senseless bullshit.
我早就搞懂了
You know-- I already figured it out.
是吗？
Really?
你知道道上规矩？
-Yeah. -You already figured the streets out?
最重要的是笑和哭
Well, it's all about smiles and cries.
拜托，你在胡扯什么？
-Put the drink down. What is that? -Hold on!
慢着，艾朗索，笑和哭
Hold on. Smiles and cries.
笑和哭，我懂了
Smiles and cries. Smiles and cries. I hear you.
你一定要能控制你的感情
Yeah, you gotta control your smiles and cries...
那是你的尊严，没人能够夺走
...because that's all you have, and nobody can take that away.
真是的
Oh, shit.
你觉得怎样？
What you think, dog?
这菜鸟能当卧底警察吗？
Think this greenhorn can handle undercover?
你当年跟他一样
You were just like him.
你也是满腔热血
Same silly-ass look and everything.
想要拯救世界
Saving the goddamn world.
才怪，现在我是哭笑不得
Now that's some smiles and cries for your ass!
我才没那么伟大
-That was you. -Shit lasted a week.
我得回去办事了
Gotta get back to it.
多谢了，很高兴见到你
Thanks for the snort. -Good to see you. -Yeah.
你有什么打算？
Yes, sir. What you doing later?
多存点钱，再熬一年就能脱身
Stay home. Save some cheddar. My dream's less than a year away.
我要去菲律宾，去了就不回头
Philippine Islands, here I come.
我跟你一起去
Let me go too.
欢迎你来
You're invited.
张开眼睛会比较舒服
Hey. Open your eyes, man. You'll feel a lot better.
坐直了
Boom! Come on, man. Sit your ass up.
你是谁？
Who are you?
我是大毒枭，你是什么人？
I'm the Zig-Zag man. Who are you?
我是警察，小心点
I'm a cop. Watch out!
别乱杀人
Don't shoot nobody.
喝点啤酒会比较清醒
Get that beer in you for ballast.
是真的，喝下去就会好过
-No, man. -Get it in you. You'll feel better.
停车
Stop the car!
快停车，有状况
Stop the car! I saw something!
快停车 好啦…
-Just relax. -Stop! All right! Hold the fuck on-- Hey!
去你的
Fuck me, man! Shit.
我是警察，快放开那女孩
Police officer! Get away from the girl!
我也要让你好看
-I'm gonna fuck you too, cop! -Get the--
我们没干坏事，是她自己发春
We didn't do shit! Bitch is crazy!
转过去，快点
Roll over, man. Roll the fuck over!
王八蛋
Fucking ass prick!
干得好
My nigger!
好耶，牛仔，你真神勇
Go ahead, cowboy, you got mad squabbles.
多谢你的帮忙 你应该开枪
-Thanks for the help. -You should've shot them.
你没事吧？
What's happening?
你死定了
You're dead!
别冲动
Okay! Wait! Hold it!
你这臭白人也死定了
-You too, white boy! -Okay....
我表哥是古惑仔，他会宰了你
-My cousins will blast you fools! -Calm down.
冷静点，你还好吧？
-Calm down. You okay? -No, I'm not!
我不好，我流血了
-Look at my nose! -I see it.
流鼻血而已，敷冰块就没事
Put ice on it. You'll be fine.
你在这儿干嘛？
What're you doing here?
搞不好他们有爱滋病
-I was just-- -They probably got AIDS.
你怎么没上课？
Why you not at school?
我正要回家
I was going to a ditch party and--
你差点就回不了家
You almost became the ditch party.
你表哥混帮派？
Where your cousins from?
山联帮，给我记住了
Hillside Trece! Remember that!
叫你表哥保护你
Tell your cousins to get your back.
拿了书包回家吧
Grab your bag and go home now.
我要她做笔录
No! I need a statement--
回家吧
Don't need no statement.
他们会把你们揍扁
They'll fuck you up.
你要放他们走？
We gonna let them go?
你想拿他们发泄就动手呀
You wanna beat them up, go ahead.
要发泄我家有沙袋
I got a punching bag at home.
他们应该坐牢的
They should be off the streets.
你听到吗？
You hear that?
你想回家还是坐牢？
Wanna go home or to jail?
你说呢？
What you think?
牢里的兄弟不是好惹的
Got room at the booty house. You been there?
他们会狠狠修理你
You'll grab your ankles.
去死吧，有人替我撑腰
Suck my dick! I know people.
你太天真了
That's how it starts.
你呢？你身上有什么？
What about you? What you got?
没有？你确定？
-Got nothing? -No. -You sure? -Yeah.
你的烟斗呢？
Where's your horn?
我没有烟斗
Got none.
但是你有钱
You got money, though.
你骗我
You lied to me!
幸好我没逼你吃下去
Lucky I don't make you eat that.
站起来
Stand up, you.
给我站起来
Stand the fuck up!
后悔了吗？
Yeah. Oh, shit, huh?
转过去，快点，转过去
Turn around, sucker. Turn around.
你喜欢强暴女人吗？
So you like raping girls?
你的嗜好是强暴女生吗？
-Like to rape girls? -No, man.
你就喜欢强暴女孩子
-That's what you like? -No....
你就爱这一套，别说谎
That what you like? Don't lie.
你不是叫我去死吗？
Told me to suck your dick. Is that what you said?
看着我
Look at me.
你是不是叫我去死？
You wanted me to suck your dick, right?
不是吗？
Isn't that what you said?
你叫我去死，别死不承认 难道我是骗子吗？
Didn't you say suck it? Don't lie. Am I a liar?
你没叫我去死，我在说谎吗？
You didn't say that?
我在说谎吗？
That's not what you said? So I'm lying?
求求你住手
No, please!
这是什么？
Where is it? I can't find it.
把裤子脱掉 快脱掉
Pull your pants down.
你要我打你哪一边的鸟蛋？
Which nut you want? I'll leave you one.
快决定，快点
Your choice. Just make a decision.
好吧
All right.
把手举高
Put your hands on your head.
闭上眼睛
Close your eyes.
要不是我有事就会割掉那话儿
Lucky I got other business.
然后塞进你的屁眼，人渣
I'd cut your fucking dick off and stick it up your funky ass. Bitch.
可恶
Damn!
我渴了，我想喝啤酒，你呢？
I'm thirsty. I want a beer. What about you?
你喝不喝？
You want a beer?
我不打扰你们了
I'm gonna leave you three to it.
臭小子
Pussy-ass bitch!
你再让我看到就死定了
I see you again, I'll fuck you up!
你连怎么死都不知道
You won't see shit coming!
我会到你背后一棒把你打死
I'll dent your mouth, I'll crack your head open.
臭警察，来呀
You fucking pig! Come on!
那女孩才十四岁
That girl's 14.
她是女人了，全身的骚劲
She all woman, though. You tax that ass for days, man!
你快滚吧
Keep walking, bitch!
来罐啤酒吧
You want a beer?
我不要喝啤酒
No, I don't want a beer, man.
你生气了？
No? You mad?
你要那六十块，拿去呀
Want to book that $60, huh?
拿去当证物
Here, go ahead, book it into evidence.
嫌犯呢？回去逮他们呀
Where the suspects? Go get them.
你把他们放走了
You let them go.
我？
I let them go?
对，就是你
You did.
你想逮人就去当巡警
You want to run and gun, stay in Patrol.
缉毒组一定要以毒攻毒
This is Investigations. Garbage men handle garbage.
我们要放长线钓大鱼
Professional anglers go after the big fish.
小毒虫会杀了你
Chasing them crackhead motherfuckers....
所以才要把他们抓起来
-They'd have killed you. -They belong in jail.
他们被打一顿，没了毒品和钱
Why? They got beaten, lost their money.
她的古惑仔表哥会把他干掉 你还要什么？
Hillside's éses will smoke them. What more you want?
伸张正义 这不算伸张正义？
-I want justice. -That's not justice?
这是以暴制暴
That's street justice.
那有什么不对？
So?
让坏人自相残杀吗？
-Let them kill each other? -God willing.
那样最好，全都死光就好了
Fuck them! Everybody looking like them.
没这么好的事，好人一定先死
Reality is, the good guys...they die first.
小学生、母亲、居家男人
The school kids and moms family men,
他们可不想被流弹打破脑袋
don't want to catch any bullets.
想要保护羔羊就要抓到野狼
To protect the sheep, you got to catch the wolf.
野狼才能抓到野狼，懂吗？
It takes a wolf to catch a wolf, understand?
什么？
What?
想要保护羔羊就要…
Protect the sheep by killing wolves.
我听到了
I heard you.
你听了也是白听
-You didn't hear me. -All right. Whatever.
随便啦 随便个头
Whatever the fuck-ever!
你几时才肯抓人？
Do you ever lock anybody up?
你都忙着把坏人放走
You seem busy keeping people out.
你在说什么？
You don't know shit!
有没有搞错，监狱是为我盖的
Shit, they build jails because of me!
法官根据我办的案子
Judges gave over 15,000 man-years of incarceration time...
判了一万五千年的刑期
...based on my cases.
我的记录辉煌
My record speaks for itself.
你抓过几名犯人？
How many felons have you got?
没话可说了吧
I rest my case.
我不嗑可卡因
I'm not smoking crack, all right?
好啦，放进置物柜
I'm glad. Put it in the glove box.
六十块也放进去
Put the $60 in there too.
以后可能用来当公费之类的
That'll come in handy. We'll use it like a credit card.
不管怎样，你做得很对
No matter what I say, you did the right thing.
我以前也是对坏人毫不留情
Reminds me when I was chasing down bad guys.
你刚才的表现很了不起
Pretty amazing shit you did back there.
谢了
Thanks.
我看到你用了锁喉功
I noticed you applied that chokehold though, huh?
那不是禁忌吗？
That's a no-no procedure.
我被打得很惨耶
I was getting my ass kicked.
所以你必须不择手段
You did what you had to do.
为了求生必须不择手段
没错
That's right.
野狼才这么做，你是吗？
What a wolf does. You a wolf?
大野狼，一起嚎叫吧
Come on, wolf! Come on, dog!
我是说嚎叫，不是咕咕叫
No, I said a wolf, not a rooster, a wolf.
那是公鸡，我要大野狼
That's a rooster, give me a wolf!
算了，把啤酒给我
Give me a beer!
拿去，这才是好兄弟
There you go! That's my nigga.
你是个聪明人，霍特
You got the magic eye, Hoyt.
你一定会是好警察
You have the magic eye.
只要多混几天就能打击毒贩
You up your street IQ you'll do some damage, I guarantee.
犯罪克星
Crime fighter.
你要什么？
What you need?
快克，二十块钱
-Crack. -Uh, 20 bucks....
快克？ 对
Crack?
我看你是警察吧
Smell like bacon! Do I look like a sucker to you, nigga?
去死吧，菜鸟
Fuck you, rookie!
追上去呀
Go fetch, dog.
你要我去…
You want me to....
饶了我吧
Oh, come on, man, it's....
帮帮忙，慢点
Give me a break! Hey, you! Slow up!
停！警察！停！
Come on, stop! Police officer! Police officer! Stop! Come on, man!
拜托，合作一点
Give me a break! Shit!
快走，你不走我就报警
Get out! Get out of here or I call police.
我是警察，请冷静点
Police officer, ma'am, calm down.
我叫你停下来
I said stop! Stop!
放开我
Get the fuck off me. Fuck off.
你不要自讨苦吃，冷静点
You're making this so much harder! Just calm down!
你很爱逮人，对吧？
You love this shit, huh?
扶他起来
Pick him up!
你们违反了我的人权
Civil rights violating motherfuckers!
小心一点
Fuck!
我的腿啦
Watch the fucking legs, man!
帮他抬起来
Pick his legs up.
你们没事干就要找我麻烦吗？
Ain't got nothing better to do than fuck with me, man? Shit!
你老板是谁？
Who you working for?
我没有老板，我是残障人士耶
I ain't work for nobody! I'm on disability!
胡说，你在贩毒
Shit! You know you cracking.
我早就不干了
I don't sell no more.
他身上没快克？
-No rocks? -No rocks.
没有，不过有这个
But I found this.
你完了
No, you don't.
那不是我的，是他栽的赃
That motherfucker planted that shit on me.
坐轮椅单挑，我肯定把他揍扁
Put me in the front seat, I'll whup his ass!
你老板是谁？
Who you working for?
我没有老板，你逼我干嘛？
Told you I don't work for nobody, man!
你的快克呢？
Where the rocks?
我没贩毒，我不干了
I got nothing on me. I gave it up.
到底在哪里？
Where the rocks?
张开嘴巴
Open your mouth.
你是医生吗？
You a doctor now?
我是牙医，快张开
A dentist. Open it.
舌头翻起来
Lift up your tongue.
拜托，他搜过我的身 我什么也没有
Your partner already searched me. I'm straight.
好吧
Yeah, okay.
你有笔吗？
You got a pen,
写字的笔？
got a writing pen?
我不知道他在追我
Didn't see the motherfucker coming!
你嘴里没东西？
Nothing in there?
没有啦
Nothing, man!
什么也没有？
Ain't got nothing, huh?
天啊
God!
可恶
Damn!
这是什么？
Now what is that?
是快克啦
Crack, man!
没错，毒虫
Right. Jimmy crack corn.
1、2、3、4、5、6
One, two, three, four, five, six.
这下你完蛋了
Oh, you federally fucked now.
你携带毒品和枪械
You got crack and a gun.
一发子弹就判十年，知道吗？
With your record you'll get 10 years per bullet, you know?
快招出来
Give me a name, now.
我不是叛徒 这下就是十年
-You know I ain't no snitch! -I know you ain't.
我知道，快说出名字
Give me a name.
二十年，快说
-Twenty. A name! -Fuck!
三十年
That's 30 years!
你想坐牢还是回家？
You want to go to jail or go home?
他正在坐牢 是谁？
-He in County. -Who?
他叫沙人，我只知道这么多
This nigga named Sandman. That's all I know! Shit!
沙人？
Sandman?
你瞧，很容易吧
See how easy it was?
解开他
Unhook him.
我受够了
Sick of this shit, man!
你想搜集证物吗？
Want the evidence?
才不要
Fuck that, man.
好兄弟
My nigga.
我是巴布 午安，巴布
-It's Bob. -Hello.
我是艾朗索，帮我查一个嫌犯
-How's it going? -It's Alonzo.
什么人？
-Got your gang book? -Why?
嫌犯的绰号叫沙人
I need a res on a Sandman.
可能正在坐牢
He may be in custody.
等等，我去查
Hold on. I'll check.
没问题
No problem.
你不能用笔插嫌犯的喉咙
That doesn't fly anymore. Shoving a pen down.
他可以提出申诉
What if he complains?
向谁申诉？ 艾朗索，113街210号
To who? 23130, 1 13th Street.
凯文米勒，绰号沙人
Kevin Miller, a.k.a. Sandman. Got it?
好，我知道地方
I know where it is.
帝国广场附近？
Out there by Imperial Courts?
没错
Exactly, uh-huh.
多谢了
Thanks a lot.
没问题
No problem.
我们要去逮捕沙人？
We go after Sandman?
我们要去逮捕沙人
We go after him.
你要开电器行吗？
Opening a Circuit City?
这些是没人认领的赃物
No, unclaimed shit from Property.
我要拿去送给线民或受害者
Hand it out to my CI's, witnesses, victims.
帮助他们的家庭
Try to help out their families.
穿起来
Put this on.
走吧
Come on, let's go.
线报说他的老婆住在这儿
Intel says she lives here alone.
可能有两名少女和一名少年
She got two female juveniles...possibly a male juvenile.
他不在我们干嘛跑来？
If he's not here, why are we?
我们有搜索票
To serve this warrant.
我们不能这么做
We can't do that.
我们是警察，想做什么都行
Yes, we can. We the police.
为什么不去申请搜索票？
Why not get a real warrant?
我们要办案
We trying to get shit done.
站过去，别害我送命
Stand over there and don't get me killed.
警察，我们有搜索票
Police, we got a search warrant!
洛城警察，开门
L.A.P.D., open up!
凯文不在，他在牢里
Kevin ain't here!
别逼我们破门而入
Just open the door!
凯文不在这儿
Kevin ain't here!
快开门，别逼我们
Open the door, ma'am!
他不在家
He ain't even here!
凯文在牢里，不在家
I said Kevin ain't even over here!
我们有搜索票，请你开门
We got a search warrant. Open up.
没有别人呀
Ain't nobody here!
趴下来
Get your big ass down! Right down! Down!
别动，双腿张开，别乱动
Don't move, spread them out! Don't move!
有别人吗？
Anybody in the house?
有没有别人？
Is anybody in the house?!
我的十岁┳拥颐状 他在卧室
My nephew, Dimitri! In the bedroom!
我要去搜房子，你搜她的身
Okay. I'm gonna clear the house, check it for weapons.
厨房没人
Kitchen's clear!
狄米崔？
-Dimitri? -Yeah?
把手举起来
Put your hands up, son.
还有别人吗？ 没有
-Anybody else? -No.
你确定吗？ 确定
-You sure? -Yeah.
留在这儿，别乱跑
Okay, just stay right there. Don't move! Don't you move.
站起来，把手伸出来
Stand up. Keep your hands where I can see them.
手伸出来，坐下来把手放膝盖
Sit down and place them on your knees.
我们是好人，你别怕
Sit down. We're the good guys.
去跟阿姨坐，快去 坐下来
Just sit down right over there next to your auntie. Right over there.
现场安全，我要进行搜查
House is Code-4. I'm starting the search.
我要看那张搜索票
I wanna see that warrant.
什么？
The what?
搜索票 你们应该给我一份副本
The warrant. I need a copy.
在我搭档那儿，他马上出来
My partner has it. He'll be out soon.
支援警力在哪儿？
Where's your backup?
帮个忙，乖乖闭嘴让我们办案
Just be quiet until we're through with our investigation.
你拿着枪，对吧，老大？
You got the gun, don't you?
没错
That's right.
臭警察、坏警察
Punk-ass, bitch-ass, crooked-ass cop!
你是菜鸟
You a rookie.
别烦我，好吗？
Give me a break, okay?
狄米崔，你还好吧？
How you doing over there?
放心，你没事，别害怕
You cool? Come on. Don't worry about it, you're cool.
好吧
All right.
女士，请你坐下来
Ma'am, please sit down.
你们跑来作威作福
You act like you pay the rent!
坐下来
Sit down!
你好臭，你一定喝了酒
You all stink! You gotta get drunk to come up here!
给我坐下来 你有酒臭味
-Sit down now! -Y'all stink!
你要向我开枪吗？
You're gonna shoot me, boss?
狄米崔，别看，臭警察要杀我
Close your eyes. This punk cop is gonna shoot me!
坐下来
-Sit down, right now! -Okay.
没事了，我们搞错了
Okay! Everything is fine. We made a mistake.
什么也没有，很抱歉
Didn't find a damn thing. I'm very sorry.
谢谢你的合作，走吧
Thanks for your cooperation. Let's go.
我要看搜索票
Show me that warrant.
什么？
What?
我要看那张搜索票
I want to see that goddamn warrant!
拿去
Here you go.
走吧
Let's go!
王八蛋
Shit! Motherfuckers!
混球，把我的钱还给我
Hey, jackers! Give me my money back.
你不是警察，把钱还给我
You ain't no police! Give me my money back!
你们还看什么？快毙了他们
Jackers, why you all standing over there?! Blast them fools!
你们最好把我老公的钱还给我
You ain't no police! I want my money back!
快发动
Start, you motherfucker!
有枪
Fuck! Gun!
快开车
Just get out of here!
别下车
Stay in the car!
放马过来呀
Yeah, motherfuckers!
该死，你不该那么做的
That was not cool, all right? That was not cool at all!
你不该在住宅区开枪
Opening fire in a neighborhood.
沙人呢？你在房间干嘛？
Where was the Sandman? What were you doing back there?
我在搜查证物
Checking for narcotics activity.
毒品、枪械之类的
Drugs, guns, baggies, you know?
还有现金
Yeah, cash!
你有话就说
Speak on it, son.
她大喊要你还钱
-She's screaming about money-- -Bullshit.
胡扯，她只想杀了我们
She's screaming about having us killed!
你会害我戴手铐穿囚服 出现在晚间新闻上
I'll be on the 6:00 news in handcuffs because of you.
政府在大力打击警察贪渎行为 我们肯定会遭殃
With the scandals, it is open season on misconduct. They'll nail us to the wall.
停车
Pull over.
-Pull over. -Here?
这是高速公路耶 停车
-Yeah, pull over. -Shit!
干什么？
What?
听好
Listen.
你只要乖乖闭嘴 招子放亮就能学聪明
You're in a privileged position to learn. Keep your mouth shut, eyes open.
你想打击犯罪就要好好学
Want to do some good, this is the place to learn.
如果你看不惯就回你的分局
You can't take it, maybe you should go back to your division.
哀求分局长让你当交警
Get a nice job lighting flares
成天指挥交通、处理车祸
or measuring car wrecks.
你必须选择当一匹狼
You got to decide whether you're a wolf...
或是一只羔羊
...or a sheep.
“生命是短暂的”
你不加入…
Get your ink...
…就去帮他忙
...or go give him a hand.
我们跑来这儿会送命的
What are we doing here? We'll get killed.
你也知道这地方？
You know about this place?
这是毒贩大本营 没错
It's the Jungle, right?
没开坦克车就不要来
They say don't come with anything less than a platoon.
不入虎穴焉得虎子
This is the heart of it.
这是丛林帮地盘
Jungle. Damu headquarters.
全是毒贩
Stoners.
这儿发生很多命案
A lot of murder investigations lead here.
只许进，不许出
One way in, one way out.
我以为我们要吃午饭
Thought we were going to eat.
我不在就别一个人跑来
Don't ever come here without me.
我是说真的，别来找死
I'm serious. For your safety.
你怎么能通行无阻？
How'd you get a golden pass?
我对他们很公平
I treat them fair.
他们太过分，我就逮人
They know if they cross the line, I tax that ass.
这是在做什么？
What's that, up there?
派鸽子通知大家知道我来了
They flipping pigeons to signal I'm here.
我来了，怎么样？
-What's up, Bone? -What's up?
你好吗？
What's up?
很好，很好
It's all good.
谢谢你帮我┳樱你真没话说
I appreciate what you did for my nephew.
别客气
For sure. For sure.
你要打给我
You better call me.
我受不了那混球
I'm sick of it. I can't stand him!
他们是谁？
Who are they?
一群混混，他们都听我的话
Nobody. I got them under my thumb.
蜘蛛，近来好吗？
-What's up, Alonzo? -All right, Spider. What's happening?
美女，看看你们，来吧
Hey, what's up, girl? Look at you. Go ahead.
这儿的辣妹多得很
All that jelly and no toast.
这是谁家？
Who lives here?
我的女人，我的小情人
Just one of my lovelies.
我的午妻，你别管
A loving touch, you know? Don't worry.
这是菜鸟杰克
New guy, Jake.
幸会，请进，欢迎光临
Nice to meet you. Welcome to my house.
替他弄点吃的
Give him some food. Take care of him.
没问题
Of course.
你好吗？ 很好
-Of course. How are you? -Good, good.
有线电视，想看什么就看
I have cable. You watch whatever you want, okay?
谢了
Thanks.
把这里当自个儿家
This is your house.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
你好吗？
How you doing?
好
Fine.
这是萨尔瓦多菜
Now, this is all El Salvadorian food.
谢谢你，很棒
Thank you. It looks great.
我得进去了
I have to go.
好吧
Yeah, all right.
走吧，我们要去开会
Let's go. We got a meeting in 15 minutes.
我要谢谢你
I just need to--
甭提了
Forget it. Let's go.
再见，小兄弟
I'll see you, buddy.
好吗？
You okay?
好吧
Here,
用眼药水
use this.
你要见谁？
Who's here?
警局的长官，不要随便说话
L.A.P.D.'s finest. Don't speak till you're spoken to.
来吧
Come on.
很高兴见到各位
Good to see you.
这是新来的菜鸟，杰克霍特
That's my new guy. Jake Hoyt.
路贾各指挥官
Captain Lou Jacobs.
你找联邦干员之前先来找他
Need to talk to the feds, go to him first.
他会帮你解决问题
He'll take your back for you.
史丹葛斯基是督察室主任
Stan Gursky, he runs the D.A. shooting team.
你开枪前最好先想到他
Think about him before you shoot someone.
杀错了人 他会让你死得很难看
If you're wrong, he'll use your nuts for dice.
道格罗西里警探
Right here, Detective Doug Rosselli...
他专门负责艺术品窃案
...handles theft cases for the French-poodle crowd.
丢了毕加索名画找他准没错 他是个好人
He's a good man.
幸会
-Pleased to meet you. -Good man.
大好人
-Should I...? -Shoo.
快滚，去吃份牛排吧
Get yourself a steak or something.
好了，各位
All right, gents.
我来见你干嘛？
I don't know why I'm meeting you.
我不跟死人讲话
I don't talk to dead men.
我还没死，老头儿
I ain't dead yet.
对不起
Fucking prick. Excuse me.
干嘛臭着脸，你家被查封了？
Why the long face, Doug? Feds seize your house or something?
去你的，艾朗索
Fuck yourself.
说那故事给他听
Tell him the story.
快说那个故事
Come on, tell the story.
你想说就自己说
If it's so funny, you tell him.
这是你的故事
It's your story.
可恶
Asshole.
好吧，有一名惯窃
All right. There's a serial burglar.
我追了他一年，他真的很狡猾
Chased him for a year. A real slickster.
上头一直在逼我破案
Captain's riding my ass the whole time.
今天准备判刑
Sentencing was today.
法官是女的
Judge is female.
没错，兰黛斯
That's right. Landers.
我知道她，她很聪明
I know Landers. She's a sharp lady.
不是吗？
No?
开庭之前
Guy gets ahold of some peanut butter,
这砘镌谄ㄑ廴了一坨花生酱
packs his ass-crack with it.
他坐在法庭等着法官宣判
He's standing before the bench, waiting to give his statement.
突然就从屁眼掏出那坨花生酱
Shoves his hand down his pants, comes out with extra-chunky Jif.
狱卒不敢靠近他
Bailiffs won't come near him.
他看着法官，并把花生酱舔光
Now he looks the judge right in the eyes and licks his fingers clean.
老天爷
Holy shit.
法官看他疯了，不能让他坐牢
So the judge says: "This man's insane. He can't go to prison."
于是判他进精神疗养院
Sends him to Psychiatric.
她上当了
She fell for it.
因为她没那么聪明
Yeah! She's so fucking smart.
等她发现了 那砘镌缇捅灰萍
By the time she found out, the guy's already been transferred.
后悔也来不及
Proceedings closed.
已经结案了
Yeah, closed.
他会住进精神疗养院半年
He'll do six months in the puzzle factory...
诊断正常后就被放走
...and they'll let him go.
连一天牢都不必坐
Never, ever do a day in prison.
我很佩服他
Give him credit.
他玩弄司法制度获得自由
He worked the system, deserves his freedom.
你真这么想？
Yeah? Think so?
也许不是
Or not.
我告诉你
I'll tell you what.
我要找到这砘锶缓蟊辛怂
I'll find this guy on the street...and I'll do him.
你最好没收他的子弹
Better take his bullets away, Stan.
可恶
Shit!
听说你这周末在赌城闯了大祸
Heard you had an expensive weekend in Vegas.
你怎么会捅这么大的篓子？
How did you ever screw up so bad?
小事一桩，我只是人生地不熟
It's nothing. I didn't know. It's not my town.
俄国佬才不管你是警察
The Russians don't care if you're a cop.
他们要杀你，你最好快逃
They'll whack you. You ought to get on a plane.
逃什么？我会搞定的
Why? It's an easy fix.
怎么搞定？
How?
我要去收一笔钱
I'll just cash in an account.
谁的钱？
Whose?
第一个线民
One of my old ones. My first one.
反正那砘锊豢煽
The guy's a high-security risk.
我被杀了，谁来监管他？
If I'm not around, who will keep him off the radar?
我只想刮点钱
I'm just taxing him,
可以吗？
that's all. Okay?
你自己决定
It's your call.
你最好别搞砸
Don't dick this up.
别跟前几个一样把事情闹大
I do not want to see you on the front page like the others.
我知道
Yeah, I understand.
你们谁开车？
Who's driving?
我，灰色宾士
Me. Gray Mercedes.
拿车
Get the car.
黑色房车，后窗被打烂了
Black Monte Carlo there, back windows shot out.
是我，可以行动了
It's me. Listen, we got the green light.
把搜索票传真去给法官签名
Fax a copy of the warrant to the clerk. Get it signed by the judge,
你跟保罗到第一地点交给我
and I want you and Paul to bring it to me.
叫杰夫带工具，十字镐和铲子
Tell Jeff to pick up some tools. Picks and shovels.
登记在维修部门的名下
Make sure he signs them out from maintenance.
对，知道吗？
Copy?
没错，动作快点
That's right. Hurry up! Later.
你拿了多少现金？
So how much cash was in that jacket?
四万元
Forty G's.
用来做什么？
What's that for?
你真的想知道？
Really want to know?
对，我真想知道
Yes, I do.
天下没有免费的午餐
Nothing's free in this world.
连搜索票都要钱
Not even arrest warrants.
可恶，我不想知道
Shit, man, I didn't want to know.
你看这个混蛋 马克，好帅哦
Check this out. Nice suit, Mark.
好漂亮的外套
Beautiful suit.
去你的
Yeah, fuck you guys!
很好，很好
All right. Nice, nice.
艾朗索，怎么样？
What's up, Alonzo?
十字镐和铲子呢？
The picks and shovels?
在后车厢
In the trunk.
你们要挖水沟吗？
Digging a ditch?
不，是你挖，好帅的外套
No, you are. Nice suit you got on there.
我早就说了
That's what I said.
帅哥，怎么样？
What up, killer?
很好，你是怎么了？
What's up with you?
道上有很多谣言
-Heard you ran into trouble. -It's all good.
没事了，我跟长官谈过
Don't worry, everything's fine.
你说没问题，我就跟你干
Shit, if we can get away with it, I'm with you.
他是什么人？
Who the fuck is this?
杰克霍特，我第一天加入
Jake Hoyt. It's my first day.
这儿可没有星巴克咖啡
You're a long way from Starbucks.
你干嘛让他参一脚？
Why the fuck is he here?
他总要有第一次嘛
Gotta get his cherry popped.
你最好别碍到我
Stay the fuck out of my way.
这儿没菜鸟的份
This is for the big dogs. Feel me?
这就是搜索票
Here it is, all legit,
有法官签名，完全合法
signed by the judge, okay?
这要多谢沙人的钱
Thanks to the Sandman. Now listen.
安全第一
Safety is first.
他敢反抗就毙了他
He gives us shit, we give him lead.
干完这一票就回家做爱
Let's do this right so we can all go home.
准备好，出发吧
Time to punch in, ladies.
别动，趴下来，快点
Freeze! On the floor!
你们跑来干嘛？
-Down! -What are you clowns doing?
菜鸟，他敢乱来就开枪
Hey, new guy, watch him!
没问题
I'm on him.
你有没有搞错？
You know what you're doing?
数到0前把手上的东西放下
Drop your gun!
5…4…3…2…
Five. Four. Three.
别逼我开枪
Give me a reason.
艾朗索会整死你们
Alonzo's gonna have your ass.
罗杰，你好
What's up, Roger?
这是怎么回事？
What's going down, brother?
没事
Oh, it's all good, baby.
没事的
It's all good.
给你的
That's for you.
我拿来干嘛？擦屁股吗？
What am I supposed to do with this? Wipe my ass?
我有坏消息
Bad news, dog.
我可以喝你的顶极威士忌吗？
Gimme some of that $300-a-glass shit.
请便
Please.
今天我跟长官们吃中饭
Had lunch with the wise men.
他们叫你乖乖付一笔规费
You gotta render unto Caesar.
他们想把我干
Those vampires want my pension.
不，没那么糟啦
No, no.
他们只是要你缴点税
Just a tax.
他们要供游艇、情妇和豪宅
They got their boats and mistresses, house payments.
我也拿他们没辄
Nothing I can do.
我只是小罗喽，我是被逼的
I'm just a lowly civil servant.
你是他们的走狗
You're their bitch.
我有什么下场？
What about me?
我会保护你
I got your back.
我不会让你坐牢的
Don't worry,
拿一点钱你不会心疼
we won't take anything you'll miss.
抱歉，我是听命行事
I'm sorry. Orders, dog.
不，你一点都不抱歉
No you ain't, cop.
提姆、杰夫和杰克跟我到厨房
In the kitchen, fellas.
去拿工具，散弹枪给我
Give me the bitch.
把他看好
You guys hold him down.
谁要把地板修好？
Who'll pay for my floor?
市政府
The city.
就是这儿
Right here.
没错了，这就是了
That's what I'm talking about.
里面有可卡因吗？
What's in here? Coke?
别急，等着瞧
You'll see.
用铁锤把锁敲掉
Grab that hammer and knock this lock off.
1…2…
One, two....
那是25万，总共有四百万
That's $250,000 you're holding. Over four million in here.
你第一天就破获三百万赃款
A $3 million bust on day one.
你说四百万
You said four.
我要抽税，天下没免费午餐
Minus tax, brother! Nothing's free in this world.
替老婆买辆车，送小孩上大学
Buy your wife a car. Put the kids through college.
不，我只领洛城警局的薪水
The only checks I cash say "L.A.P.D."
这砘锸羌俚姥
Somebody didn't sleep through Ethics.
你不想分一杯羹吗？
You don't want a piece of this?
不想
No, right?
不能这样，我不要
Not like this. No.
你不要？
No?
第一次不习惯，我替你保管
First time, you're not comfortable. I'll hold it for you.
你习不习惯？
What about you?
我很习惯
Oh, I'm comfortable.
你习惯吗？
How about you?
我早就习惯了
I'm very comfortable.
准备收工吧
Let's wrap this up.
什么也别碰，这都是证物
Don't touch a thing! Evidence.
那群老头儿在想什么？
Alonzo, what are those pricks thinking?
他们都把我当死人耍着玩吗？
That I'm gonna stand still and let them horsefuck me?
我倒是可以打死你
Could put you out of your misery.
拿去
Hey, Jake, here.
坐下来
Sit down.
我跟你说个秘密
Here's a secret:
你只要杀了嫌犯
When you kill someone on duty...
他下辈子就得当你奴隶
...they have to be your slave in the afterlife.
动手吧
There you go.
开始养奴隶吧
Start an entourage.
你要我杀了他？ 对
-Shoot him? -Yeah.
给我个痛快吧
Come on, kid. Do me a favor. Come on.
帮个忙，毙了他
Do yourself a favor. Hit him.
你是说真的？
Are you serious?
把百叶窗拉上
Hey, close the blinds.
好，我开枪 快呀
-All right, I'll shoot him. -Go.
杀了他
Shoot him.
不行
No, man.
年轻人真没用，你不开枪？
Kids these days. Not gonna do it?
给我吧
All right, give it to me.
菜鸟
Rookies!
要办事非得自己动手
You want shit done, you gotta do it yourself.
我的天
Holy shit!
呼吸
Come on, breathe.
呼吸，对了
Breathe, there you go.
放松
Just let it go.
呼吸
Breathe, dog!
他死了
He's finished.
这里
All right, Jeff.
杰夫，你在门口中弹
You took fire coming in.
我是想休假啦…
I need some time off, but....
拜托，瞄准一点
Watch the shades.
好啦
All right.
好了吗？ 来吧
-Ready? -Kiss me.
第一枪
One....
你没事吧？ 没事
-You okay? -Yeah.
我要再开一枪
I gotta give you one more, though.
来吧
Do it.
可恶
Fuck!
真相没人信，证据才重要
It's not what you know, it's what you prove.
这是破案经过
Here it is.
马克和保罗把门撞开
Mark and Paul kick the door.
杰夫冲进来被罗杰开了两枪
Jeff's in first. Roger fires twice.
怎么？射到了？
What, one go through?
你射伤他了
You shot him!
你射到我了
You fucking shot me, man!
你会得到奖章
Don't worry.
快叫救护车
Call an ambulance!
你想坐牢还是回家？
Go to jail, or go home?
让我先把证词套好
All right, here's the scenario.
马克和保罗撞门，杰夫冲进去
Mark and Paul kick the door. Jeff runs in.
罗杰开两枪打中杰夫
Roger opens fire, hits Jeff.
菜鸟霍特接着冲进去
Hoyt is in second,
用散弹枪把罗杰解决掉
drops Roger with the shotgun.
谁杀了罗杰？
Who shot Roger?
菜鸟，他开的枪
New guy.
菜鸟毙了他
你看到什么？
You two?
霍特把他轰死
Hoyt.
去他的，叫救护车啦
Fuck Hoyt. Ambulance time!
好了，快通报吧
Done. Paul, call them up.
这是刑警，有警员中枪受伤…
11-49. 998. Shots fired. Officer down. Repeat, officer down. 5951 Baxter Street.
恭喜了，你会获颁英勇奖章
Congratulations. You're gonna get a medal of valor for this.
我没杀死他
I didn't shoot him.
一屋子的警察都说是你
Four cops saw it.
不是我，是你
But I didn't. You did.
一名洛城警局缉毒组警官
"An L.A.P.D. narcotics officer was killed today...
今天在办案时不幸殉职
...serving a warrant in Echo Park."
把枪给我
Give me the bitch.
警局发言人表示该警官留下…
"A spokesperson said the officer is survived...
一名妻子和幼女
...by a wife and child."
你无路可退了，懂吗？
There's more. You get the picture?
我懂了
Yeah, I get it.
你拿枪指过我两次，事不过三
That's the second time you pointed a gun at me!
乖乖，我就知道你很厉害
Goddamn, boy! That's it, Jake!
你们都看到吗？
Y'all see this? That's it!
我很乐意替你毙掉他
I'll put a bullet in that melon.
慢着
Wait, wait.
放心，把枪放下
I'm gonna be cool. Drop the gun!
尽管下手吧，我要找他陪葬
Shoot me. He's coming with me.
我要开枪了
I'll shoot!
他是联邦干员
He's a fed.
他不是
No, he ain't.
他只是刚正不阿的乖乖牌
He's just a kid that got the drop on y'all.
大家放轻松把话谈开，好吗？
Let's take a deep breath and just diffuse this. Jake?
你不能害我，我不要犯法
I didn't sign up for this!
我知道你很生气
I know you're angry.
大家把枪放下
Everybody, put the guns down.
不行
Hell, no.
乖乖牌先让步
Choirboy first.
把枪放下，这是我的命令
Listen! That's an order! Put them down!
仔细听我说
Use your ears, Jake.
有时候你一定要面对事实
Sometimes we take this shit all the way.
这就是现实的残酷
It's the nature of the business.
下次没有人会逼你开枪
You'll never have to pull the trigger again, all right?
你要转到哪里？
Mark, where are you transferring?
重案组
S.I.S.
他升了警探
Detective.
我会在一年半内让你升官发财
You give me 18 months, I give you a career.
破获巨额赃款、逮捕头号要犯
We make the big seizures, Jake.
你一旦加入了就要完全投入
But if you're in my unit, you gotta be in it all the way.
我以为你办得到，我错了
I thought you were man enough to handle this shit.
五名资深警官都说是你开的枪
Five decorated officers say that you shot Roger.
调查员会替你抽血验毒
They will check your blood for intoxicants.
他们会发现什么？
What are they gonna find?
你成天都在嗑药
You've been smoking PCP all day.
你计划了一整天
You've been planning this all day.
我计划了一整个礼拜
All week, son.
你敢乱说话我就让你去验血
You talk, your blood gets to the lab.
你只要出门逛街马上血溅五步
You wanna take a walk? You won't make it out of here.
不过你只要合作就是英雄
If you're cool, you're a hero.
你是没杀过人的菜鸟警察
You're above suspicion.
另一把手枪还剩两发子弹
Alonzo, there's two shots left.
我们杀了菜鸟就说是罗杰干的
We need to kill him now and say Roger got him.
不，我们不杀人
No, we ain't killing nobody.
他是个好人，也是个聪明人
This is a good man. I can feel it.
这是震撼教育，我们都经历过
Just had a little freak-out, that's all.
他会合作的，谁也别杀他
I say he's cool. Nobody's gonna hurt him.
不过你要做个决定
You do have a decision to make.
十秒后一大堆警察会冲进来
Because this place is gonna be overrun with blue suits.
你可以到外面
So why don't you please go outside,
好好想一想
clear your head.
或是杀了我
Or shoot me.
保罗
Hey, Paul?
你死定，听到了吗？
You're dead, motherfucker! You hear me?!
你死定了
Dead!
别一直吃
Well, lay off the device.
好
All right.
浴缸要洗干净
Make sure that tub is clean.
好吗？
All right?
好，待会见
All right, later.
你没事吧？
You all right?
这次你最好别乱来
It behooves you not to dick around on this one.
这算是自卫杀人…
Justifiable homicide in the line of duty.
这算是谋杀和抢劫
-Now, what happened-- -What happened was murder. And armed robbery.
警察就有权杀人吗？
We had badges, so it's different?
张开双眼吧，你看不到吗？
Son, open your eyes! Can't you see?
他是你朋友，你却一枪杀死他
That man was your friend, and you killed him like a fly.
朋友？为什么？
My friend? Tell me why?
就因为他认识我？
Because he knows my first name?
我只是利用他，这是我的职责
This is the game. I played his ass.
这也是你的职责
That's our job.
罗杰卖毒品给小孩
Roger sold dope to kids.
这世界没有他会更安全
The world's better off without him.
他是全洛杉矶最大的毒枭
This man was the biggest major violator in Los Angeles.
我盯了他十年了
I watched that cocksucker for years
现在我逮到他
and now I got him.
干这一行要斗智斗力
This is chess, not checkers!
难道闯进他家把他铐起来
What'd you think? We'd roll up in a black and white?
说：你被捕了 就能解决问题吗？
Slap the cuffs on him?
他可是大毒枭耶
He's a high roller, dog.
把钱拿去吧 我说过，我不要
-Take the money. -I'm not taking it.
我不要这笔钱
-Just take it. -No!
那就那去煎炒煮炸都无所谓
Look, I don't give a fuck,
你拿去大伙儿会好过些
but the boys'll feel better.
我才不管他们
Fuck their feelings!
你这样就不算我们一伙
Jake, we're a team.
一伙？
A team?
你们是一伙疯子
You guys are fucking insane.
我宁愿去当交通警察开罚单
I'll go back to the Valley, I'll cut parking tickets.
警察不该是这样
It can't be like this.
就是这样 抱歉让你看到丑陋一面
It is. I'm sorry, but it is.
但这是必要的
It's ugly, but it's necessary.
我当警察的目的是抓坏人
I became a cop to put away dealers and criminals,
不是自己当坏人
not to be one.
你跟我以前一样
You sound just like me.
我知道你的感受，你很害怕
I know what you're going through and feeling. You're scared.
我才不怕
I'm not.
你怕得要命 第一次都会这样，我也是
Yes, you are. Everyone goes through that the first time. I did.
只要你接受残酷的现实世界
The sooner you match what's in your head with what's in the real world...
心里就会好受很多
...the better you'll feel.
干缉毒这一行一定要犯点错
In this business...
别人才会信任你
...you gotta have dirt on you to be trusted.
等你想通了 美好世界会等着你
When all this is behind you, a whole other world will open up for you.
我就是你的向导
I walk a higher path, son.
我能为你开启每一扇门
I have the keys to all the doors.
你在说什么？
What do you mean?
我的手下不是做领导的料 他们都是小丑
My guys aren't leaders, they're clowns. You're a leader.
你才是领袖，你可以取代我
You want my job? You got it.
你想抓坏人 这才是最好的机会
You want to lock up poisoners? This is the place to do it.
但你要有耐心，先升上警探
But you gotta take your time. You'll make detective,
学聪明点，然后再做改变
you'll grow wise. And then you can change things.
不过你得先改变自己
But it's gotta be from the inside.
我待会带你回总局找史丹
Let's go downtown to the station. Talk to my guy, Stan.
他会教你该怎么跟检察官说
He'll go through what you gotta say to the D.A.
我们来这儿干嘛？
What are we doing now?
我的线人坐牢
I told an informant
我答应要照顾他家人
I'd take care of his family for him.
我都替他们带些吃的用的
Bring them food, stuff like that.
帮他养家活口
Gotta help out the family.
信不信由你，我都在做好事
Believe it or not, I do try to do some good.
干嘛？你来找死吗？
You know where you're at, dog?
看什么看？
The fuck you looking at?
我带了好东西来
Hey, we got some things for the family.
厨房在这儿
Kitchen's this way.
放在柜台
Put it on the counter.
我去一下厕所，等我出来就走
I'm gonna go to the head. Two seconds, we're gone.
真好，我要雷射唱盘
Hey, let me get the CD player.
果汁机给你，我要雷射唱盘
No, the CD player's mine.
卓梦，给我进来
Dreamer! Come here!
到房间数一数
Count that shit, all right?
拜托，我正在忙耶
Thanks a lot, I was busy.
下次你最好自己数
Learn how to count, fucking math whiz.
你偷看牌
-You looked! -I didn't.
才没有，你说我出老千？
You calling me a cheater, ése?
再发一次牌
Deal again, Sniper.
你玩牌吗？
You play cards, cop?
不常玩
No, not really.
喝啤酒吗？来一瓶吧
Want a beer? Have a cold one.
不，谢了
No, thanks, I'm good.
坐下来，玩一把嘛
Come on, sit down. Play a card game with us.
你是客人，有点礼貌
Don't be rude, ése. You're a guest.
坐下来玩一把
Why don't you play one hand?
放心，我们不赌钱
Don't worry, we ain't betting money.
我们马上就走了
We gotta roll in a second.
艾朗索在大号，没那么快
Alonzo's taking a shit.
好吧，我就玩一把
All right, I'll play one hand.
你们在玩梭哈吗？
Is this five-card draw?
小丑是王牌
Yeah, jokers are wild.
告诉我，你当猪猡多久了？
Why don't you tell us something? How long you been a pig?
对不起，对不起
My bad. My bad.
我是说你当警察有多久？
I meant a police officer.
我当了19个月
I've been a pig for 19 months.
是吗？
Is that right?
你喜欢吗？
You like it?
我应该当消防员，还要一张
I should've been a fireman. One more.
你有什么牌？
What you got, dog?
三张十一点
Three of a kind.
我什么也没有
I didn't get shit.
太棒了
Boo-ya, baby!
我有两对，两对耶
Two pair!
你高兴什么？警察赢了
What the fuck? He won.
拜托，我有两对耶
I got two pair!
三条比你的两对大啦
Three of a kind beats two pair, you fucking dumb truck.
你真是笨，你一定没吃药
You're fucking stupid. Take your medication.
听好了，我才是聪明人
Seriously. I know I'm number one.
因为有这呆瓜，我们才不赌钱
See why we don't play for money? Because of this vato.
很好，给我看你的砘
Show me your cohete.
什么？
What?
你的佩枪，给他看
Your gun, homes. Underneath your shirt.
你用的是点三八口径手枪吗？
What is it, .380 stainless?
九厘米贝瑞塔
9mm Beretta.
像这一把吗？
Like that?
一模一样
Just like it.
真的吗？
Yeah?
这就是问题了
Here's the problem.
我看过这把，我要看你那把
I seen this one. I want to see yours.
来啦，我不会开枪的
Come on, ése, I ain't gonna shoot nobody.
给我看看
Let me check it out.
那招是在警校学的？
Learn that in the Academy?
是呀
Neat trick.
挺厉害的
This is nice.
不错，这真不错
Nice.
一枪就把坏蛋给毙了
You could fuck a vato up with this.
你只要拿起来瞄准对方
What you do is, you aim like that.
我只是在耍你
I'm just playing.
我得走了
Yeah, I gotta go.
艾朗索
Alonzo!
留下来玩吧
Kick back and party.
你走不了了
Ain't nothing out there for you.
什么意思？
What are you talking about?
白小子
Hey, white boy.
既然你都问了，我就说吧
If you ask me homes, that's just, of course, if you ask...
艾朗索出卖你了
...Alonzo played you, ése.
他把你害惨了
Big time.
等一等，你想去哪？
Wait, where you going?
该你发牌了
It's your deal.
钱都在这儿
It's all there.
你确定？
Sure?
你不信就自己数呀
You can count it yourself.
艾朗索一定有魔法
Alonzo pulled off a miracle.
时机很差，他却弄到这笔钱
Times are tight. Scared up a lot of cash.
他杀了谁？
Who'd he jack, homes?
我不知道
I don't know.
他杀了罗杰
He jacked Roger.
把那砘锖涞袅
Blasted that fool.
艾朗索是个贪污腐败的坏警察
Alonzo's a low-down, ruthless vato.
不过我很佩服他，他够狠
But I like that.
不，我才不会跟他握手
That's why I never shake his hand.
他什么都不尊重
He don't respect nada.
他弄那笔钱干嘛？
Know what the money's for?
艾朗索太火爆了
Alonzo, he's a hothead.
上礼拜在赌城
Last week in Vegas,
有一个俄国佬把他给惹毛了
some Russian starts talking shit.
他把对方活活打死
Alonzo, he just snapped. Beat his ass to death.
结果这俄国佬是重要角色
Turns out, that Russian, he's a somebody.
艾朗索欠他们一百万美元
Now, Alonzo's into the Russians for a million.
你怎么知道？
How do you know that?
艾朗索今晚一定要付钱
Alonzo has until tonight to pay up.
要不然就会被追杀
But he's still on their list.
想不到他真的弄到这笔巨款
Nobody thought he could get the cash.
幸好他有一组手下替他干活
Good thing he did. They're looking for him.
今晚午夜他没赶到市区交钱
If he don't turn up downtown with the cash by midnight....
你老友就死定了
Your vato...he's dead.
你被别人鸡奸过吗？
Hey, pig. Ever had your shit pushed in?
快回答
Simple question.
没有
-No? -No.
我被鸡奸过
Had my shit pushed in.
没错
Yeah, man.
我也被鸡奸过，好惨哦
I had my shit pushed in, bro! Big time!
史麦利呢？
Smiley?
我也被别人鸡奸过
Sure, I always get love from the homeys.
你们把他揍扁了
You guys fucked him up!
把她们带走
Go next door.
快滚出去
Get the fuck out of here!
你完蛋了
You fucked up.
你被捕了，臭警察
You're under arrest!
谁叫你在我家撒野
For being a cop, dogging me in the mouth in my own pad.
你会被毒打一顿，小杂种
You got the right to be bitch-slapped!
把他拖进浴缸
Drag him to the tub.
动手吧
Raid his ass!
关门，声音会很大
Do it! It's gonna be loud.
我先拿他的钱
Let me get his money.
快点
-Wait. -Hurry up.
史麦利
Smiley, check it out.
你铁会生气 这不是你表妹吗？
Is that your little cousin?
你从哪儿拿来的？
-What's this? -I found it!
我检到的，我检到的
-Who had it? -I found it!
哪儿？
Where?
我在麦卡锡公园检到的
I found it in MacArthur Park! MacArthur Park!
等等，我看不到
Wait up, I can't even see.
给我闭嘴
Shut the fuck up!
信教的话就祷告吧
Get in your last prayer.
听我说，她当时被强暴
Listen to me, man. She was being raped.
我阻止两个毒虫强暴她
Two crackheads were attacking her...
我发誓，我阻止了他们
...and I stopped them! I swear to God!
你在说谎
You're lying to me!
我发誓我没说谎
I am not lying!
她被强暴，我阻止他们
She was being raped! I stopped them!
我有一个小孩
Please! I got a kid.
闭嘴
Shut up, fag!
毙了他吧
Blast his ass.
我有一个小女儿
I have a little girl!
下手吧
Do it!
她是我表妹，我要问清楚
I'm gonna get to the bottom of your bullshit. She's my cousin, homes.
她只是小孩，不该把她扯进来
Ain't right involving her.
你完蛋了
You fucked up.
要是你敢说谎
If you're lying to me...
我就打爆你的鸟蛋
...I blow your balls off.
莉蒂，你在干嘛？
-Hello. -Hey, Letty.
表哥，我在做功课
-What's up? -Hey, Smiley. Just doing homework.
你要找汤尼吗？
You want Tony?
我要找你，你今天有上学吗？
No, I want you. You go to school today?
有啊
Yeah.
你没有翘课吗？
-You didn't ditch? -Nope.
我都有上课呀，怎么了？
I went to every class. Why?
听说不是这样
I heard different.
警察找过你吗？
Cops talk to you today?
没有
No, no.
老实说，别骗我
All right, Letty... don't bullshit me.
好啦，我被两个毒虫攻击
I got jumped by two crackheads.
你被攻击？
You got jumped?
我猜他们想强暴我
I think they wanted to rape me.
他们只打了我几下而已
But nothing happened, okay?
有个警察跑来救我
Because this cop came.
他差点没命，不过他很神勇
They almost killed him ...but he kicked their ass.
这警察长什么样？
Describe him.
他是白人，蛮年轻的
He was a white boy. He looked real young.
你真的没事？
You're okay?
没事啦，我很好
Yeah, I'm fine.
莉蒂，这件事以后再说
-Hey, Letty. -Yeah? -We're not done.
好吧
Okay.
怎么样？
What's up?
你要不要毙了他？
You gonna blast him?
他说的是实话
Vato was telling the truth.
真没想到
Life's a trip, qué no?
真是太巧了
This is some trippy shit.
看在你救了我表妹的份上
That's for getting my cousin's back.
拿去，别把地板弄脏了
Cover your head. You'll mess up my floor.
你知道这只是公事公办
You know this was just business, right?
对吧？
Right?
对
Right.
菜鸟，来找死吗？ 你不能来这里
What you doing here? You know you don't belong here.
你有事吗？
You got business here, rookie?
我来找艾朗索
I'm here for Alonzo.
你爸在吗？
Hey. Is your dad home?
他在卧室
In the bedroom.
他在卧室吗？帮我开门？
He's in the bedroom? All right, you wanna open up the door?
你在看电视吗？
Okay. Thanks. You watching TV?
好看吗？
Yeah, anything good on?
你要我叫妈咪吗？
Do you want me to call my mom?
不要
No, I don't.
这样好了
I'll tell you what I want.
我要你躲起来，有地方躲吗？
Find a good hiding spot. Do you have a favorite place to hide?
衣橱
The closet.
这间衣橱吗？太好了
In the closet? That's perfect.
打开来，对，很好
Okay, open up the closet. All right. Good, good.
我要你坐下来
Can you sit down in there?
待在这儿
All right. Now stay in here and be very quiet.
别出声，我马上回来
I'll be right back. All right?
全都在这儿
It's all good, baby.
你靠着墙壁
You, against the wall.
你把手伸出来
Move real slow.
钱放在袋子里
Put the money in that bag...
把枪放进枕头套
...take your weapons and place them inside that pillowcase.
恭喜了
Congratulations, son.
你没有死
You made it.
你通过考验，你是缉毒员了
You passed the test. You're a narc.
把枪放下，别害她心脏病发作
Put the gun down before you give her a heart attack.
钱放袋子里，枪放进枕头套
I said put the money in that bag. Place your weapons inside that pillowcase.
你别想去见俄国佬，来不及了
Fuck your appointment with the Russians.
好吧
Oh, okay.
把枕头套给我
Okay. Hand me the pillowcase, baby.
Baby! Hand me the pillowcase.
你想把我带回局里？
You're gonna book me?
别忘了你嗑了药
You smoked the dust.
你也像疯子一样打死罗杰
You ran out, and you're the one that shot Roger.
拿去吧
Here you go.
还有你脚上的佩枪
And the one on your ankle?
背后那把也要吗？
Want the one in my back pocket too?
对
One problem:
问题是你没有目击证人
You got no witnesses.
谁是证人？罗杰？史麦利？
Who are your witnesses, huh? Roger? Smiley?
我的手下才不会帮你
You think they'll help you?
真相没人信，证据才重要
It's not what you know. It's what you can prove.
你能证明什么？
What can you prove, huh? Nothing.
你哪来的证据？
-Where's your evidence? -There.
那笔钱
Oh, shit!
决斗开始了
It's on now, Jake.
别动
Don't move.
你在哪里？
Where you at, Jake?
出来吧
Come on out, dog!
我看到了
-Ah! I see you. -Shit!
我可是神枪手
I'm surgical with this bitch.
你想死得很难看吗？
How you want it?
坐轮椅的砘镆彩俏业慕茏
That fool in the wheelchair? How you think he got there?
你看到吗？
You see what I see?
霍特警官
Officer Hoyt,
警察的天职，拯救人命
job number one: Preserve life.
别伤害我儿子
There's my son. Don't hurt him.
我们一起走出来
We're walking out together.
你没事吧？
You all right?
我要找妈咪
I want my mommy.
我知道
I know, I know, I know.
别乱动，不会有事的
Just sit tight, all right?
我知道
It's gonna be all right. I know.
手伸出来，他人呢？
All right, let me see your hands! Where is he?
窗口
-The window. -Come on!
快来抱你儿子
-Get your kid, stay down. -Alonzito!
羔羊手上有枪可不好玩吧
It's no fun when the rabbit has the gun, is it?
好砘
My nigga.
谁先一枪毙了他
Hey, first Damu puts one in his head...
我就让他发财
...I'll make you a rich man!
快呀，谁想发财？
Come on now. Who wanna get paid?
谁想发财？
Who wanna get paid?
他们跟你不一样
They're not like you.
我今天学到一件事
You know what I learned today?
我也跟你不一样
I'm not like you.
很好，那敢情好
That's good. I'm glad to hear that.
很好
Good.
现在怎样？
So, what now? Huh?
你要杀我吗？
What you gonna do, shoot me?
你要杀一个警察吗？
You gonna bust your cherry killing a cop?
动手呀
There it is, Jake.
杀了我
Hit me.
你没杀过人吧？
You never killed nobody before.
这跟踩死蚂蚁不同
It ain't like stepping on ants.
男子汉才能杀人
Takes a man to kill.
你是男子汉吗？
Are you man enough to kill?
轰了我脑袋
Hit me right there.
杀我，杀了我吧
Get me, Jake. Get me.
动手呀
Hit me. Hit me.
你下不了手
You can't do it.
帮我把这砘锉辛
Somebody drop this fool for me.
我们受够你了，你自求多福吧
You got us twisted. You got to put your own work in.
好吧，就是这样吗？
All right. It's like that, Bone?
就是这样
It's like that.
我跟你杠上了
Player to player, pimp to pimp.
我不相信你会开枪
I don't believe you'd shoot me.
别逼我
Don't do it.
Don't.
我不信你有种开枪
I don't believe you got it in you.
我要把枪和钱都拿走 而你却不敢怎样
I'm gonna get that gun and that money. You ain't gonna do a thing.
因为你不敢从背后向警察开枪
You ain't gonna shoot no cop in the back.
别逼我
-Don't do it. -You know what you'd get?
杀警察会进毒气室
The gas chamber. You know what it smells like?
毒气闻起来就像松油
Pine oil.
我要把你送上西天
That's where you headed, to pine oil heaven.
我要拿枪，然后拿钱
I'm gonna get that gun and that money.
我不信你有种向我开枪
I don't think you got it in you. I'm gonna go get it.
可恶
Shit!
你这小王八蛋
Ah, you motherfucker!
下一枪就毙了你
The next one will kill you.
小杂种
Son of a bitch!
你打中我屁股
You shot me in the ass!
好，等一下，听我说
Okay, wait, wait, wait. Okay, okay.
我需要那笔钱，快给我
All right. Come on, I need the money. Give me the money.
杰克，快把钱给我
Give me that money!
办不到
It's not gonna happen.
你要杀了我，抢我的钱？
You gonna take my own money from me?
这是证物，你想坐牢或回家？
That's my evidence. You wanna go to jail or go home?
我想回家
I wanna go home, Jake.
把钱给我让我回家
Give me the money, and let me go home.
你想回家？
You wanna go home?
对，让我回家
Yeah, let me go home, Jake.
把钱给我，让我回家
Give me the money, and let me go.
Give me the money, and let me go home, Jake.
快点
That's right, come on.
你不配当警察
You don't deserve this.
好吧，小混蛋
Okay, motherfucker.
杰克，你走，快走吧
Jake, go and bounce, homey.
我们会掩护你
Get up out of here. We got your back.
什么？
What?
就是这样
-It's like that. -Oh, no, you didn't!
不，你不能这样，你不能这样
Wait a minute! No, you-- Hey, hey, Jake!
杰克…杰克…
Hey! Jake! Jake!
回来
Jake, come back here!
杰克
Jake!
你这个忘恩负义的臭小子
You disloyal, fool-ass, bitch-made punk.
我需要那笔钱
I need my money!
杰克
Jake!
你们这群混球，好吧
Oh, you motherfuckers! Okay.
我要把你们全都关进大牢
All right! I'm putting cases on all you bitches!
你们一个都别想逃
Huh? You think you can do this shit? Jake!
你们竟然这么对我？
You think you can do this to me?!
我要让你们一个个都蹲苦窑
You motherfuckers will be playing basketball in Pelican Bay when I get finished with you!
每天做苦工
Shoe program, nigga!
永远不见天日
Twenty-three hour lock-down!
我才是这儿的老大
I'm the man up in this piece!
你们最好别把我惹毛
Who you think you fucking with?!
我是警察老大，你们是老百姓
I'm the police! I run shit here! You just live here!
没错，快躲起来
That's right, you better walk away.
因为我要把这地方给拆了
I'm gonna burn this motherfucker down!
大金刚都动不了我
King Kong ain't got shit on me!
没关系，没办法
That's all right. That's all right.
管它的，反正我是赢家
Shit, I don't fuck-- I'm winning anyway. I'm winning.
怎么样我都赢，我不会输
I'm winning anyway. I can't lose.
我就像是一只打不死的蟑螂
Shit, you can shoot me, but you can't kill me.
今天真倒霉
Oh, what a day.
今天有够倒霉了
What a motherfucking day!
一名洛城警局缉毒组警官
An L.A. police officer was killed today...
今天在办案时不幸殉职
...serving a warrant near LAX.
警局发言人表示艾朗索警官…
An L.A.P.D. spokesperson said Officer Harris...
留下一名妻子和四名幼子
... was survived by his wife and four sons.